Dream big. Dance free.
High Strung Free Dance is a music, romance, drama
film directed by Michael Damian.
Zander Raines, a dazzling and tempestuous young choreographer, gives the break of a lifetime to two hopeful artists when he casts a stunning
contemporary dancer, Barlow, and innovative pianist, Charlie, in New York’s most-anticipated new Broadway show: Free Dance.
But the move throws off the show’s delicate creative balance when Charlie
falls hard for Barlow, while Zander embraces her as his muse.
Zander, played by Thomas Doherty.
Charlie, played by Harry Jarvis.
Barlow, played by Juliet Doherty.
Oksana, played by Jane Seymour.
Ravi, played by Ace Bhatti.
Rose, played by Kika Markham.
Nicholas Dimitri Constantine Galitzine ( GAL-it-seen; born
29 September 1994) is an English actor.
After his acting debut in The Beat Beneath My Feet (2014), he appeared in an episode of the television series
Legends, and had leading roles in the 2016 teen drama films High Strung and Handsome Devil.
He later starred in the supernatural horror film The Craft: Legacy (2020) and the musical film
Cinderella (2021), also contributing to the latter's accompanying soundtrack.
Galitzine's break-out role was the romantic drama Purple Hearts (2022).
He achieved further prominence for romantic dramas Red, White & Royal Blue (2023), and The Idea of You (2024),
as well as the comedy film Bottoms (2023) and the period drama series Mary & George (2024).
In addition to acting, Galitzine has been a global menswear ambassador for fashion house
Fendi since 2023, and global fragrance ambassador for Emporio Armani since 2024.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.